Since flat files are human readable,
بما أن الملفات الثابتة قابلة للقراءة بواسطة المستخدم،
you can easily write your own code to parse or understand these files using Base Python.
يمكنكم بكل بساطة كتابة الكود لتحليل هذه الملفات وفهمها باستخدام Base Python.
Open the file, read the text line by line,
افتحوا الملف، وأقرأوا النص سطرًا تلو الآخر،
separate each line's content by the delimiter,
افصلوا محتوى كل سطر باستخدام المحدد،
and store everything in your data structure of choice.
وخزنوا كل شيء في بنية بيانات من اختياركم.
But people have come for us and solved this problem
لكن أتى الأشخاص وحلوا هذه المشكلة لنا
and created libraries with a ton of additional functionalities,
وقاموا بإنشاء مكتبات مع الكثير من الوظائف الإضافية،
especially for data wrangling, analysis, and visualization.
وخاصة تعارض البيانات والتحليل والتصوير.
A library like pandas, for example.
مكتبة مثل pandas، على سبيل المثال.
Pandas can handle pretty much every file type imaginable,
تستطيع pandas معالجة كل أنواع الملفات التي يمكنكم تخيلها،
and is especially well-suited for tabular data.
وتعتبر مناسبة تمامًا لبيانات الجدول بشكل خاص.
The code to read comma separated data into a data frame is super simple.
تقرأ الكود البيانات المفصولة بفاصلة في إطار البيانات بسهولة بالغة.
We use the read_csv function.
نستخدم دالة read_csv.
And there's our pandas data frame for the best of our t.CSV file.
وهناك إطار بيانات pandas لدينا للحصول على الأفضل من ملف t.CSV
But the file we wanted to use is actually a TSV file, bestofrt.TSV.
ولكن الملف الذي نريد استخدامه هو في الواقع ملف TSV، bestofrt.TSV.
That's tab-separated, and that's okay.
هذا tab-separated، وهذا لا بأس به.
Since there's no clear standard for flat files,
بما أنه لا يوجد معيار واضح للملفات الثابتة،
pandas has one main function for parsing them,
فإن pandas لديها دالة رئيسية واحدة لتحليلها،
and it is read_csv.
وهي read_csv.
Read_csv can handle all kinds of flat files, including TSV files.
دالة read_csv تعالج جميع أنواع الملفات، بما فيها ملفات TSV.
You just need to change the parameters to fit your specific use case,
كل ما تحتاجون إليه هو تغيير المعلمات لكي تلائم حالة الاستخدام المحددة،
like changing the separator parameter set, for example.
مثل تغيير مجموعة المعلمات الفاصلة، على سبيل المثال.
Or whether or not entries are quoted and more.
أو ما إذا كانت المدخلات بين علامتي اقتباس أم لا وأكثر.